search:  

[Home](https://microcosmpublishing.com/) / Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

### Who we are

Our website address is: https://microcosmpublishing.com

### What personal data we collect and why we collect it

By default, we do not collect any personal information. If you sign-up for our newsletter, create an account, place an order or begin to place an order, or fill out a contact form, we will collect the data you enter (such as name, email address, purchase history, comments).

### Accounts and purchases

When you sign up for a Mycosm account on our website, we will keep the information you enter indefinitely; you can log in and view and change this information.

When you make a purchase on our website (or begin to place an order), we will retain this information for our own records and in order to communicate with you about past, current, and future orders.

### Comments

We keep comments that are left on our product pages indefinitely. If you delete your account, your comment will remain under the name “deleted user.”

### Contact forms

We keep contact form entries indefinitely for customer service. This information is not shared with anyone else.

### Cookies

We set a temporary cookie to keep track of items you put in your shopping cart. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we use the same temporary cookie to identify you as a logged-in user. If you select “Remember Me”, a separate cookie will be set, and your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the remember-me cookie will be removed.

### Analytics

We use Google Analytics, which has its own Privacy Policy.

### Who we share your data with

We do not share any of your personal data with anyone.

### How long we retain your data

If you sign up for an account or make a purchase, any information you provide is retained indefinitely.

If you sign up for an account on our website, we store the personal information you provide in a user profile. All users can see or edit their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

### What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, you can request to receive any data we hold about you. You can also request that we delete any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

### Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

### Your contact information

If you have any questions or would like to request access to your data or deletion of your data, please write to us at privacy@microcosmpublishing.com

### How we protect your data

Our website is secured via a Let’s Encrypt SSL certificate.

#### Microcosm Publishing

**Open for pickups and deliveries only**  
Mon—Sat, 11am-3pm  
2752 N Williams Ave  [map](http://goo.gl/maps/SvXcq)  
Portland, OR 97227  
  
**Want to contact us?**  
Please read [our FAQ](https://microcosmpublishing.com/faq) first  
(360) 291-7226  

* **Hang out with us on social media!**
